After that,
tell me more
[praise]
Hello friends, my name is Sachi and
I welcome you to your own YouTube channel Wealth.
Friends, in today's
video we will talk about ICICI
Lombard General Insurance, its
result of the quarter has come, so we will see
how the result of Jeevan is, along with that we will
also see some of its old finance assistants,
still we will look at some fundamental rights in it
and in the last we will check how is
its target prize winner and whether
we should invest in it or not
and after that we will do it to qualify the labels,
who has time for it, New Delhi
and which support will
show the effect, which secrets can be seen, you can find it
in my kitchen, click on that also in
this video, stay tuned to the video.
Talking about the result of Jeevan, you
can see here the June 2030 is
circled, last year's June quarter is here
and the March 2020 quarter is here, so
if you compare the net sales thing,
you can see that June 2019  If we
compare it to less than 2003, then you can see here that there was some growth around here
and if we
take March part, then you
can see that only a slight decrease is being seen here.
Talking about net profit, friends, it will
often be difficult here, you can see that it has
increased from Rs 309 crores to Rs
98.10 crores, a lot of growth is being
seen here from the quarter of 19 to
June 20 quarter and if we consult the March-2010
records,
even more growth is being seen here,
friends, let me compare it with the revenue growth of its industry,
then friends,
in the last five years, its decline has been
17.14 friends,
whereas if we talk about district average growth, then it is
coming out at 11.6, so
its revenue growth is more than the revenue of its industry,
which is a very good
thing. After the market, then friends,
its growth in the market is 0.4  It has increased from 1.5 percent to
4.38 percent. Knowledge is
coming out of coffee. It is about data from its water.
Friends, I have a three-year-old
son here at the time of scanning 18,
19 and 20. If we talk about total revenue here,
you can see that there was a rise in 1819
and 19. Now we are seeing a rise in it. Talking about
net income, friends,
here you can see that my pattern will be
seen, rise in 1819 and 1920,
for you we need and DSP of CBI, rise in 1819
and there is a rise in between.
Friends, if we talk about that, first of all we
will check the investment Chakli system, it is
interesting, but if we talk, we
can see, but the current price is
not moving forward. If we
talk about returns, then the returns are quite good in the
stock and Digit is
not providing that good attractive sir. It is being
said that the entry point is quite
good. Please tell me, this volume does
not do Chandra Bhilai and there are no side effects of any kind in the stock.  It belongs to
insurance,
it is a stock of the sector of the
last step. If we talk about the stock market place, then
again if we talk about the strength and ranking, then
after a few minutes, then friends, you
can see the PA of the sector, here it is 20.83 and if we
talk about this stock appeal, then it is coming out to be 59.04,
if we talk about 14% ease here
at 67, I believe that
we should talk about it, if you
talk about its share holding pattern with friends, then
you can see that the promoter holding is
coming out at 189,
if we talk about the missile in June 2019, you
can look at 10, its position before this year
was till the top of the text, which is
180, total till now
in the negative at 3.6 in the cent of cars and if you
subscribe, it has cooled down from 30,
now if we talk about skin rights, then
subscribe, subscribe,
click on like and subscribe button, then you
can see and see here and above MS Word
Especially this channel is getting difficult to
see here and
friends, this was delivered in promoter holding,
now see, this happened just some time
ago and you will remember, here
you had set up your vested interest in
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
so that by sending money to it, it
can strengthen and strengthen its balance sheet, hence here
in a little note, this trick was sealed, there is a
file in that house, if we talk about its price
focus, then you can see
that the current track is coming out of Twenty20, so
from here it is being told
that by July 2011, the Amit market
price which can be seen, can be
seen on your side by sending it on cement rate, which will come to
₹1370, the price is seen going with these, so that
2%, that is, under the
influence of dormant yoga, you have 1574 and their salary
falls, you have 2% less return in 2030  Look, I
can see the price,
meanwhile, friends, let's talk about some points of this, you
can see the top inside it, if we
talk about the first point, then it is shallow guardian
license poster 28.4
famous hair growth in June quarter net
profit and profit yesterday how much per training
his appointment above 8.1 crore, if we
talk about them then profit word brother and
improvement in the combined graduate and
lower capital gains, so
due to the improvement in this,
we have seen the profit which has increased here,
finally talking about capital
gains, lower bike shift 1% Airtel's
worry and in quarter of sciences compare
₹2 138 and in the year ago periods, if we
talk about mind, then the commander is limited to 280,
quarter one compare 28.4 president of ago
period,
friends, so the gross
domestic premium which has come out has been solved,
add 5.3 per cent, it has declined ₹2
302  Crore in water dynasty here is domestic
premium income there we have to
see a little dry from 5.3 percent but were
respectful and that has always seen profit after
hiding inside the scooter,
friends so respect to the individual
business statement later inside writing was
reported in the maritime fire group
health retail and drop important if we talk then
motor insurance hot scene
underwriting loss in the year poster and
profit 94 crore in June quarter grand
car was driven by that time was returning so one
person will do it so now you will see in school
friends before moving ahead in the video let
me tell you do
not forget to like and subscribe the video so that
in the latest video friends if I talk in front of you then
you can see that it was
listed in that month in 2017 it
peaked and after that you can see if you
drive a little bit after that there was a decline here
and after that if you talk from June 2018 then it was
very dangerous what we have seen here
and later we saw that
due to the depression of Corona we saw a decline in the shares
and last  Talking about for match,
you can see that now in white hut it is
seen that this is of the
month of April, May or June and this like is
going on, even in this we have not crossed the whole month,
so here we are
seeing appointment, overall you can see
that it is trying to catch up by loosening its old labels,
friends, if we talk about Monday's content,
you can see that if we talk about it, then
53.71 comes out which is
quite good, but hopefully
we will see some restriction in it, now we are
talking about 4 of these, friends, so
you can see that the processor of MS Word here is
not yet there, but the
white line is almost close to
giving it the opportunity of the railway line, so
when we have the guidelines here, turn
off the white light
and after that we will mix a little, the police can
see in four, stop Chand,
now see, for quite some time you can see
that the straightening that it is doing inside the jail, the
municipality is not very suitable download Mumbai right now  It's
giving, if you see inside this box, it's been
running for a long time, so
we'll wait for its processor to give and
after that we'll position it inside so that
we can go and see an award protest.
Friends, if you talk about elastic entry,
you'll see a big green color here
and that's why the results were going to come
within 20 minutes. Last Friday itself,
I had some very good
results in it, that Hanuman Devta had been inside people, due to which
we got to see that police friend inside it.
If we talk about it,
you can see that during this time the ladies
took their leave and cut it and also
cut our Berlin German medical line and took an appointment and have also
given a very good lift upstairs
and are blocking the medium size of their fiber right now.
Friends, the neck inside it is of the press level, you
can see that you are coming out at
1380.
Now you can see that it had hit this high level twice before,
once at this time and once at this time,
and since then  There was a
fall in it, so now its
patrolling is around 280, from here we can
easily understand till at least 30, it
is formed within the potentials and we will be able to
see it on Twitter, but
Abhijeet Chakli, right now we do not have to do it inside it,
as I told you, we
will wait for the crossover of Remedy, if we
see this cross going up in it
and after that if you make it, then there are
chances of the meeting coming down, we will
see it a little less and now we can see the side's
3061 only in the features
and with this we end the video,
thank you bye take care